[{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":18779,"timeElapsed":70960},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980285149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4649,"timeElapsed":75611},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980289050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3899,"timeElapsed":79512},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":16239,"timeElapsed":95752},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":9742,"timeElapsed":105496},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980326181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":11146,"timeElapsed":116643},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5755,"timeElapsed":122399},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980337842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5903,"timeElapsed":128304},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6070,"timeElapsed":134375},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":21354,"timeElapsed":157648},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3259,"timeElapsed":160908},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3574,"timeElapsed":164483},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":7895,"timeElapsed":172380},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2858,"timeElapsed":175239},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2931,"timeElapsed":178172},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":180752},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980393991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3700,"timeElapsed":184453},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980396682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2690,"timeElapsed":187144},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":11099,"timeElapsed":199924},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3378,"timeElapsed":203304},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4935,"timeElapsed":208241},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2986,"timeElapsed":211228},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2810,"timeElapsed":214040},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3915,"timeElapsed":217956},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1963,"timeElapsed":219920},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2395,"timeElapsed":222316},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2747,"timeElapsed":225064},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":11571,"timeElapsed":237932},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2635,"timeElapsed":240568},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980452614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2506,"timeElapsed":243076},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3402,"timeElapsed":246480},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2370,"timeElapsed":248852},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465990,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7599,"timeElapsed":256452},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3163,"timeElapsed":259616},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3987,"timeElapsed":263604},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":266393},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2562,"timeElapsed":268956},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7635,"timeElapsed":278084},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3106,"timeElapsed":281192},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494826,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4095,"timeElapsed":285288},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3699,"timeElapsed":288988},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":291824},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980503574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2211,"timeElapsed":294036},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2127,"timeElapsed":296164},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2267,"timeElapsed":298432},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"118","question":"What is your biggest vanity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2402,"timeElapsed":300836},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8094,"timeElapsed":310212},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980522538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2787,"timeElapsed":313000},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980528642,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6102,"timeElapsed":319104},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4603,"timeElapsed":323709},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2883,"timeElapsed":326593},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980538822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2690,"timeElapsed":329284},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2459,"timeElapsed":331745},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2466,"timeElapsed":334212},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2715,"timeElapsed":336928},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2326,"timeElapsed":339256},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8255,"timeElapsed":348908},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3739,"timeElapsed":352648},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3083,"timeElapsed":355733},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4851,"timeElapsed":360586},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2658,"timeElapsed":363245},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2834,"timeElapsed":366080},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2875,"timeElapsed":368956},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":371536},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2579,"timeElapsed":374116},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":12031,"timeElapsed":387269},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2930,"timeElapsed":390200},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4043,"timeElapsed":394245},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980607154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3370,"timeElapsed":397616},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2290,"timeElapsed":399908},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980611899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2451,"timeElapsed":402361},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2195,"timeElapsed":404557},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2654,"timeElapsed":407212},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"147","question":"Tell the names and approximate ages of your family members, as well as where they were born (to the extent you know this information). Include grandparents and aunts and uncles.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2130,"timeElapsed":409344},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":11530,"timeElapsed":422240},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2691,"timeElapsed":424932},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2850,"timeElapsed":427783},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":430220},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1922,"timeElapsed":432144},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2350,"timeElapsed":434496},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2163,"timeElapsed":436660},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2387,"timeElapsed":439048},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"138","question":"Do you read a newspaper or online news source and which do you prefer? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2675,"timeElapsed":441724},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9615,"timeElapsed":452524},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2467,"timeElapsed":454992},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2930,"timeElapsed":457924},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2370,"timeElapsed":460296},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1816,"timeElapsed":462113},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1857,"timeElapsed":463972},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1827,"timeElapsed":465800},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":467736},{"subjectID":"ms5dx3xkgs","prolificID":"60d1129ad29dbe85a59b9c4a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2663234b54b63decad8","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2306,"timeElapsed":470043}]